THE SUB-MAN
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠
瞧瞧他
There he blows.
老兄 他就他妈是只雷龙
Bro, he is a fucking brontosaurus.
总想干到天亮 但从没硬起来过
Always wants to fuck, but never can get hard.
兄弟 大战前把敌人妖魔化是好事...
Dude, it's good to demonize the enemy before...
-知道 知道  -在你务必取他首级前
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. - It's good to demonize him
把他妖魔化确实是好事
before you have to kill his ass.
-弟兄们呢  -这是必须的
- Siblings? - You have to.
弟兄和家眷们快来
Siblings and partners.
那啥 提前说一句 我想让威拉一起拍...
OK, just so you know, I want Willa in this. So...
这样...
OK. Is that...
-这样合适吗  -康纳
- Is that appropriate? - Connor.
当然 没事 很合适的
Oh, no. That's fine. It is appropriate.
好吧 但还是... 合适吗
OK. But is it... is it appropriate?
这样不会出现问题吗
It's not gonna be problematic?
怎么会 完全没问题
No, it won't be problematic.
康纳 过来
Connor, come here.
-威拉是应召女郎  -现在不是了
- Willa's a call girl. - Not anymore.
而且... 有一天这事会爆出来
And... sometime it might come out
波及我的形象 或是汤姆的形象
and hurt my profile, or Tom's profile,
我也不想伤了和气
and I don't want to be horrible,
但拜托啦
but come on.
你能理解的吧
You get it. Right?
好 我理解
OK, I get it.
但如果你不愿意
But if you don't allow it,
我会对着汤姆的脸来一拳
I'm gonna punch Tom in the face
然后撕裂我的衣服
and I'm gonna rip my shirt open,
直接就地拉一坨黄金
I'm gonna take a fuckin' dump on the ground.
我会发狂 因为她是我爱的女人
I'm gonna go apeshit, because she's the woman I love.
你能明白吗 好
Do you get it? OK.
-你来吧  -你太古怪了
- You're in. - You're so weird.
行 大家都到齐了吗
OK, is that everyone?
-拉瓦  -拉瓦 快来 进来
- Rava. - Rava, come on. Get in.
-拉瓦 来吧  -对 对 快来
- Rava, come. Come. - Yeah, yeah, go on.
-就站这儿  -好 都到齐了吗
- Get right in there. - OK? Is that everyone?
罗曼 我会拍下这张
Roman, I'll take that one,
但咱能为夫妻们拍一张严肃点的吗
but can we do a serious one for the parents?
-好  -这个...
- Yeah. - Is that...
罗曼 罗曼 严肃点
Roman. Roman. Do it seriously.
好了 一 二 三
OK. One, two, three.
翻译: 宇宙万宝路
翻译: 负能量小天使
翻译: Ciaran
翻译: 咩咩恩
翻译: 渡渡
翻译: 走油肉
翻译: 橙砸
时间轴: Heiforn
时间轴: 阿布
特效: 小布
后期&压制: Jason肖
校对:渡渡
校对：宇宙万宝路
继     承
第 一 季  第10集
"无人失联"
监制: 宇宙万宝路
我刚添加了一条说明
I just added that we're not subject
我们不受任何融资条件的制约
to any financing conditions.
行
Mm-hmm. OK.
挺好
Yeah.
-这个打印三份  -行
- Print three of these. - Yeah.
好 那我想剩余的唯一问题就是
OK, so, I guess the only question left is this:
谁去给他送信
who actually is gonna deliver it to him?
-等下 你逗我呢  -我们必须确保
- Wait, are you serious? - Well, we have to make certain
他亲眼看过这信了
that he has had eyes on it.
当然 我知道 但我以为是你去
Yeah, I know, but I assumed you.
这个嘛
Right.
我以为是你
I assumed you.
行 我只是觉得如果我们要计划
Fine, I just guessed if we were planning to
搞死你爹 然后赚得盆满钵满
fuck your dad to death to make our fortune,
我可能会主动请缨
I might offer to actually do the fucking.
-你是怕了吗  -没有啊
- Are you scared? - No.
去你妈 你怕了吗
Fuck you. Are you?
是啊 兄弟 我吓尿了
Yeah, man. I'm scared.
所以如果我害怕 而你又他妈假装不害怕
So if I'm scared and you're fucking pretending not to be scared,
那肯定是他妈你去送啊
then fucking you should do it.
伙计 认真的吗
Dude. Seriously?
杰西也可以
I mean, Jess could do it.
行 管他妈的 我能行
Fine. Fuck it. I can do it.
咱们到底准备好了没
OK, are we ready or what?
抱歉 应该打出来了的
Sorry, it should be printing.
但没有吗
But it's not?
糟了
Uh... shit.
-怎么了  -我觉得它顺着
- What? - I think it got sent
无线网络发送到另一台打印机上了
to a different printer on their Wi-Fi network.
你他妈开玩笑呢 杰西
Are you fucking serious, Jess?
-发到哪儿了 杰西  -不知道 上面没显示
- Where is it, Jess? - I don't know, it doesn't say.
操了 那...
Oh, fuck. Wha...
你... 你必须找到 杰西
Uh, well, you... you need to find it, Jess.
-立刻 马上  -好 好 好
- Like now. Now. - Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
是谁 站住
Hello? Hey? No!
搞鸡毛呢 滚出去
What the fuck! No! Not now!
啥...
Wh...
你还好吗 小家伙
Hey. How ya doin', buddy?
-耳环  -项链
- Earrings. - Necklace.
-伙计  -好哇
- Hey. - Hey.
对不起 儿子
Hey, I'm sorry, kiddo.
兄弟 还好吗
Bud, you OK?
发生什么了
Hey. What happened?
-我...  -怎么...
- I... - What...
我把他当成别人了 吼了他几句
I thought he was someone else. I shouted.
抱歉 我不是故意吼的
Sorry. I didn't mean to yell.
现在才下午五点 肯 你还好吗
It's like five in the afternoon, Ken. You OK?
当然 好得很 我很好
Yeah, I'm great. I'm good.
-就是 要干些大事  -可不是
- Just, uh, some big moves. - Mm-hmm. Sure.
好吧 那你走之前要吼自己另一个孩子两句吗...
OK, well, you wanna yell at your other kid before we go, or...?
-我们回头见  -好
- We'll see you later. - OK.
那啥 我们晚点见 好吗
OK. Hey, listen, I'll see you guys later, OK?
杰西好像拿到了 你该去看看 以防万一
Hey. Jess thinks she has it. You should go, just in case.
-好  -你能行吧 开干吗
- OK. - You good? We doin' this?
当然 开干吧
Yeah, I'm doin' this.
你会电邮格丽和董事会吧
You'll email Gerri and the board?
会 只要送到了告诉我就行
Yeah, just tell me when it's delivered.
啥意思 你觉得我会打退堂鼓吗
What, you don't think I can deliver it?
不 就是 只有15%的人
No, it's just, only 15% of men,
谈到这种事时
when it comes to it,
会射杀一名手无寸铁的敌军
actually shoot an undefended enemy soldier.
他先开枪的
He shot first.
...卫星
...satellite.
作为一个礼物 我觉得很屌
As a gift, I thought it would be cool
如果我们能在大屏幕上直播
if we could show it live on a big screen.
不 绝对不行 我不想看到
No, absolutely not. I don't want to have
一根巨屌在我的婚礼上爆炸
a big fucking dick blasting off at my wedding.
-那他妈不是巨屌  -当然是 是艘火箭啊
- It's not a big fucking dick. - Yeah, it is, it's a rocket.
不是火箭或屌的错
It's not the fault of rockets, or dicks,
它们只是外形恰好符合空气动力学
they both happen to be aerodynamic in shape.
你简直是朵奇葩 没门儿
You're unbelievable. This is not happening.
-你好  -你好 玛西娅
- Hello. Hi. - Hi, Marcia.
我爸有空吗
Is my father available?
一切都还好吗
Everything is OK?
都好 其实... 我有话跟他说
Yeah, it's... I just need to have a word.
进来吧
Come in.
洛根 肯德尔来了
Logan. It's Kendall.
告诉他 如果他想阻止我买报纸和电视台
Tell him if he wants to stop me buying papers and stations,
他就可以滚了
he can fuck off.
我们可以出发了
We're good to go.
过来吧 儿子
Come on through, son.
你... 要不你出来吧 老爸
Do you... maybe want to come out, Dad?
不 你进来吧 我又没蹲厕所
No, come on in. I'm not on the can.
服务还不错 对吧
Nice service, right?
可惜不是天主教牌的 勉强凑合了吧
Pity it wasn't Catholic, but there you go.
那些小屁孩毁了这个品牌
Fuckin' all those kids hurt the brand.
那个
Hey.
这恐怕不是什么好事
This isn't a nice thing, I'm afraid.
对 看看这个
Yeah. Read this.
-这是啥  -这是...
- What is it? - It's...
一份以每股140美元收购韦斯达股票的提议
a proposal to buy Waystar for $140 a share.
我们要求你坐到谈判桌边 开立新账
We're asking you to come to the table, open the books.
这样啊
Uh-huh.
股东会看得起这个价格
It's great value for shareholders.
-这样啊  -对
- Uh-huh. - Yeah.
就这样 我不会... 投入任何私人感情
There it is. I'm not... gonna get into feelings.
你他妈在跟我玩熊抱吗
Is this a fuckin' bear hug?
没错
That's right.
-不行  -好吧
- No. - Well, fine.
我们有融资
We have the financing.
咱们就听听大家的想法
Let's just see what everyone thinks.
情况就是这样的
You know, this is just the situation that has arisen,
而且... 你很强硬
and... you're very tough,
我也是如此 虎父无犬子
and so am I, as your son,
所以我觉得 我们之间必须采用这种手段
so I think this is just the way it has to be with us.
我... 我不为我做的一切感到抱歉
I'm... I'm not sorry for what I'm doing,
因为都是对的
which is correct,
但是我... 我为让你难过而感到抱歉
but I... I'm sorry for how it makes you feel.
我很抱歉 选了今天这个日子
And I'm sorry it had to be today.
这脱离了我的掌控
It was out of my hands.
-给你  -不行
- Here. - No.
给我滚
Fuck off.
你清楚自己干这事是为了什么吗
Do you even know what you're doing this for?
想法...
Ideas...
我... 我一直想做成些事情
I... I have, you know, have wanted t-to do things
-然后呢  -拯救我们的公司 然后是...
- Uh-huh, uh-huh. - to save the company, and...
然后做...
and do...
然后做... 做一些事...
just do... do things that are...
看到没 你他妈连话都说不利索
You see? You can't even fuckin' say it.
我能... 我能... 说清楚
I can... I can... say it.
老子听着呢
Then say it.
做... 一些好事
Do... some good things.
做好事
Do good things.
你他妈去当护士啊
Be a fuckin' nurse.
你好
Hey.
玛西娅
Marcia!
怎么了 你干什么呢
What is it? What are you doing?
格丽 格丽在哪 还有卡尔
Gerri. Where's Gerri? And Karl.
卡尔在纽约呢 洛根 怎么了
Karl is in New York, Logan. What is it?
我需要格丽 我需要卡尔 我需要...
I need Gerri. I need Karl. I need...
把手拿出来 拿出来吧
Get out of there. Get out of there.
快来
Come on.
怎么了
What is it?
熊抱
Bear hug.
它会...
It'll... Ohh.
他们要来恶意的
They'll go hostile.
难怪 那就说得通了
It fits. It makes sense.
-今天吗  -我不知道
- Today? - Oh, I don't know.
我他妈不知道
I don't fuckin' know.
我目前所处的位置并不好
It's not a good position I'm in.
要是他们有融资
If they have financing,
和大股东
and major shareholders,
我在这里 那明天...
and I'm here, and tomorrow...
明天之前 我需要...
by tomorrow I need...
我需要一大堆目前没有的东西
I need a lot of things I don't have.
失陪一下
Excuse me.
伊维斯议员 我是康纳·罗伊
Hey. Senator Eavis. Connor Roy.
超级怀疑论者
Huge skeptic.
怀疑一切
Massive skeptic.
-很高兴知道  -对啊
- Good to know. - Yeah.
社会主义吗 我对你以及
Socialism, huh? Wow! I got a big problem with you
你所代表的一切都有异议 我的朋友
and everything you stand for, my friend.
-你好 宝贝  -你好
- Hi, baby. - Hey.
-你还好吧  -我好得很
- You good? - Yeah, I'm good.
听我说 我看着你
Listen, I look at you
我看到了魏玛 我看到了恶性通货膨胀
and I see Weimar, I see hyperinflation.
魏玛共和国: 在1918年到1933年间采用共和宪政政体的德国 曾经历恶性通货膨胀
看着你的脸 无意冒犯 我看到了死亡的婴儿
I look at your face and, no offense, but I see dead babies.
-你懂我的意思吧  -那可就有意思了
- You know what I mean? - Well, that's very interesting.
我没法同意 不过...
I can't say I agree, but, um...
我能失陪一会儿吗
Look, would you excuse me for a minute?
当然 议员先生 很高兴和你比划了一会儿
Oh, yeah. Great to joust a little, Senator.
对
Yeah!
他就这点能耐了吗
That's the best he can do?
康纳 他会成为下一任总统
Connor, he's gonna be the next president.
真的吗 我刚在辩论里拿他洗地了
Really? I just wiped the floor with him in a debate.
他的智力检测没过关
He buckled under intellectual scrutiny.
刚才那段没录下来算他运气好
He was lucky that wasn't televised.
就是他了吗 你就是因为那位
Is it him? You don't want a rocket launch
嘟囔议员不想发射火箭吗
'cause of Senator Bluhhh or whatever?
一艘装满穆斯林即食麦片的火箭能帮上忙吗
Would it help if it was a rocket full of Muslim granola?
罗曼 不要 我只是不想我的婚礼上有火箭
Roman, no, I just don't want a rocket at my wedding.
别这么幼稚了
Stop being a kid.
"我是小西 我是个成年人 我很重要"
Oh. "I'm Shiv. I'm an adult and I'm important
因为我给一位戴着眼镜的人做事"
because I work for a man with glasses."
顺便一问 他是犹太人吗
Is he a Jew, by the way?
-得了吧  -怎么了
- Oh, come on. - What?
就是个简单 友好 有一点点种族歧视的问题嘛
It's just a simple, friendly, slightly racist question.
别这样啦 你以前很有趣的
Oh, grrr! You used to be fun.
什么时候成他们那种人了
When did you become one of them?
-谁们  -就那些巧言令色的人
- One of who? - Like dancey bullshit,
"哎呀 我们不能那么说"之类的人
like, "Oh! We can't say that" Kind of people.
抱歉我不想参加你那随心所欲
I'm sorry I don't want to come to your freewheelin',
自我放纵 胡言乱语的土风舞会
good-time, N-word-shoutin' hoedown.
N开头的词[黑鬼] B开头的词[贱货] C开头的词[臭逼]...
N-word, B-word, C-word...
这世界又不是个糟心的幼儿园
the world isn't fucking nursery school,
没人喜欢被管教
and people don't like to be taught.
好吧
Oh, right.
我很欣慰你一直在看我们的节目
Well, I'm glad you've been watching our programs.
你不该那么做 毕竟你的智商理解不了
You shouldn't do that, not with your IQ.
抱歉 我要去看一场
Excuse me. I actually have to go watch
由我负责的于日本进行的
a fuckin' satellite launch in Japan
破卫星发射... 等我会儿...
that I'm actually in charge of, that... Hold on!...
我专门为你重新安排的
that I reorganized for you,
而你太他妈碳中和[环保]了 欣赏不来
but you're too fucking carbon-neutral to enjoy.
喂 我看到了
Yeah? Uh, yep, I got it.
正在直播 正在连接
It's streaming, it's connecting.
行了
Yeah.
好了 没有 还行
OK, no. It's good. It's good.
祝各位好运 行吧
Wish everyone luck, OK?
当然用日语说
In Japanese, obviously.
快啊
Come on.
有了
There we go.
刚才真的很难
That was really hard.
是啊 兄弟
Yeah, man.
你他妈做到了
You fuckin' did it.
酒
Drinks.
酒 酒 酒
Drinks. Drinks, drinks, drinks, drinks, drinks.
这他妈就对了 喝酒
Fuck yes, drinks.
真棒
Yes.
杰西
Jess?
-好呀  -庆祝一下
- Hello.  - Celebration.
我们来他妈庆祝一下
It's a cele-fuckin'-bration.
你做到了 兄弟
You did it, man.
太爽了
Oh! Yes.
爽歪歪
That's good.
我的飞行员还在值班吗
Are my pilots still on the clock?
看看他们谁有时间载我回家
Check if any of them have the hours to fly me home,
或者已经安排了
or scheduled.
但别让自己看起来很慌
But you don't want to look panicked.
是啊
Yeah.
明天再回吧 也许
Tomorrow, maybe.
格丽 那件事怎么样了...
Gerri. Where are we on the...
晚点会召开紧急电话董事会议
Emergency phone board meeting for later.
今晚吗 还是明天
Tonight? Or is that tomorrow?
明天吧
Tomorrow.
他们得有更多的钱 和更好的准备
They're gonna have deeper pockets, better prep.
看看那操蛋的干瘪加州葡萄干在哪
Find out where that fuckin' shrunken California raisin is.
叫上总统 聪明
The President. I think that's smart.
快点 快点 我们走吧
Come on, come on. Let's go.
融资很困难 我们需要政治支持
The financials are hard. We need political support.
我们赶紧走吧
Let's get goin'.
-威威  -亲爱的
- Will.  - Hey.
听着 宝贝 我有件事要告诉你
Listen, baby, I got something I need to tell you.
好的 一切都...
OK. Is every...
我们去那边说
Let's go over there.
就在国王画像旁边 完美
Right by the kings. This is perfect.
-好的  -好吧
- OK.  - Mm-K.
-好的 听着...  -什么事
- OK, listen... - Yeah?
我想我终于找到想做的工作了
I think I finally found a job I want to do.
好吧 是什么
OK, what is it?
美国总统
President of the United States.
什... 好吧
Wh... OK.
-怎么样  -真的吗
- Yeah?  - Really?
你看起来并不激动
You don't look excited.
怎么会 听起来像是个有趣的计划
No, sure, sounds like a fun project.
-你因为话剧生我气吗  -不是
- Is this about the play?  - No.
我很喜欢的
Because I loved it.
是啊 你不想浪费钱让它放映
Sure. You don't want to waste your money putting in on,
但竞选总统 就是合理的投资吗
but running for president, that's a sound investment?
而且 我计划花钱去 你知道
Plus, I'd be planning to spend on, you know,
确保你的历史清干净了
making sure your history was cleaned up.
总统啊 威拉 这是大事
The president, Willa. This is big.
当然 但你知道 没什么比艺术更有力量
Sure, but you know, nothing's more powerful than art.
可不是 当然 你懂的 除了行政部门的权力
No, sure, you know, apart from the power of the executive branch.
戏剧能改变思想
Drama can change minds.
是 但也不太能啦
Yeah, but not really.
我可以取缔戏剧 虽然我不会这么做
I could outlaw drama. I mean, I never would,
我只是在阐述这个位置的权力有多大
but I'm just illustrating the power of the position.
-好吧  -不过 没错 艺术
- OK.  - But, right. Art.
罗曼
Roman?
来见见丹尼斯·林顿
Meet Denis Linton.
丹尼斯是警察
Denis is police,
而且他还是什么专员
and he's also the something commissioner?
警察与罪案事务专员
Police and Crime Commissioner.
对的 总之 他很早就认识你爸和我
That's right. Anyway, he knew your father and me
那时他的工作比这还无趣
back when he was doing something even more boring.
-对吧 丹尼  -谢谢你照顾我们
- Isn't that right, Denny?  - Thanks for lookin' after us.
-怎么样  -什么
- Hey. How was it?  - Yeah?
-卫星发射呀  -对 它
- The launch.  - Yeah, it,
-不好意思 你说什么  -发射怎么样
- I'm sorry, what?  - How did it go?
他最近在协调一个卫星发射
He's been coordinating a satellite launch.
-真不错  -怎么样了
- Fascinating.  - How did it go?
还... 不错 实际上 很不错
It, uh... Great, actually. It went great.
-是吗  -是啊
- Yes?  - Yeah.
太棒了 祝贺你
This is amazing. Congratulations!
-太棒了  -谢谢 很令人激动
- Fantastic.  - Thanks. It's very exciting.
去拿杯喝的吧
Go ahead and get a drink.
-好的  -庆祝一下
- Oh, yeah.  - Celebrate.
好的
Ok.
好啊
Well.
看看你
Look at you.
洛根 今晚 我们要不要...
Logan. For tonight, shall we...
今晚 今晚...
For tonight. For tonight...
我能给您倒满吗 先生
Can I top you up, sir?
什么玩意 混蛋
What the fuck?! Jerk!
这下好了
Oh, great.
对不起 先生 我不是有意...
Sorry, sir, I didn't mean to...
是啊 但你洒了 你这蠢货
Well, you did, ya fucking prick.
走吧 滚开 滚出去 滚开
Go on, fuck off. Get out of here. Fuck off!
-先生 我以为你说要  -别再嘟囔了
- Sir, I thought you said yes.  - Stop mumbling.
别看着我 给我滚出去
Don't look at me! Get the fuck out.
你在哪找的这些人啊 菜鸟
Where do you find these people, huh? Amateurs.
我不想再看到他了 一次都不想 一次 明白吗
I don't want to see him again. Ever. Ever. OK?
你觉得你能帮我找点更烈的酒...
Do you think maybe you can fetch me something stronger to...
-当然  -谢啦 谢谢
- Sure.  - Thanks. Thank you.
怎么了 我能帮忙吗
Hey, what's up. Can I help?
我在忙着处理... 另一个问题
I'm very busy with... on another matter,
但你知道这件事吗
but are you across this?
我接到了四十多个关于发射的电话
I've had 40 calls about the launch.
不 真奇怪 我好像没接到任何电话
No, that's weird. I haven't gotten any, I don't think.
-它爆炸了  -它爆炸了
- Yeah, it blew up.  - It blew up?
对啊 它在发射台上爆炸了
Yes, it exploded on the launch pad.
好吧 真奇怪...
OK. It's weird...
是哦 他们真应该告诉我的
Yeah, they really should have told me that.
这真是 真是麻烦
That's, that's naughty.
情况有多糟糕 很糟吗
How bad is it? Is it bad?
我重复一次
I'll reiterate.
它爆炸了
It exploded.
就在发射台上
On the launch pad.
所以 是啊 我觉得非常糟糕
So, yeah, I'd say that's bad.
有没有 比如
Are there, like,
-死人吗  -对的
- Dead people?  - Yeah.
好吧 这我不知道
Well, I don't know.
是的 这种规模意味着有可能会有人员伤亡
Yes, I mean, the scale means there's likely casualties.
情况很不明朗
It's very unclear.
因为我确实施加了很大压力来加速这次发射
Because I did put a lot of pressure to accelerate the launch,
尽管有些人表示担忧
even though there were concerns.
-真的吗  -对的
- You did?  - I did, yeah.
操
Fuck.
我只是觉得如果能
I just thought it would be nice
在小西婚礼这天发射会很棒
for it happen on Shiv's wedding day,
像烟花 像盛大的烟花
like fireworks, like big fireworks?
-好吧 这被你说中了  -我告诉你这事
- Well, you got that right. - I'm just telling you
因为我发了很多关于它邮件
because I sent a lot of emails about it,
而且隐瞒也没什么用 因为...
and there's no use hiding that, because...
我只是想说
I just want to say I think
你作为总顾问 多少要了解下情况
it's for you to know, as general counsel,
这样你才能保护我
so you can protect me?
好吧 我尽力
Well, I can try.
但是 操 你可能面临共同过失杀人罪指控
But fuck, you're looking at potential corporate manslaughter.
就在这里签名
If you can just sign there.
让我们欢迎... 新娘新郎
I give you... the bride and groom!
今天是非常值得纪念的一天
This has been a very memorable day,
这一天 好吧 我...
a day that, well, I'll...
只要我活着 我就永远不会忘记
I'll never forget as long as I live.
而且我希望它是完美的...
And I wanted it to be perfect...
完美的... 为了小西
perfect... for Shiv.
的确很完美
And it is.
没有人 没有人会破坏它
No one, no one can ruin this.
能被那些我们深爱 信任
It's wonderful to be surrounded
并且非常珍视的人包围真是太好了
by those that we love, trust, and hold very dear.
因为没有什么比家人...
Because there is nothing more important...
更重要了
than family.
所以...
So...
敬家人
to family!
To family!
他在开玩笑吧
He's joking, right?
打扰一下
Excuse me.
你好...
Hi. Um...
明天我们去伦敦怎么样
so, how about we do London tomorrow?
好的
OK.
我列出了一份投资者电话清单
I put together a list of investor calls.
卡尔将进行初步接触
Karl will make initial contact.
还有毒丸计划 应该考虑一下吗
And a poison pill, should you consider it?
是的 我将为我们的毒丸防御提供选择
Yeah. I will have the options for our poison pill defense.
所以你要在25号见总统
So you have the president in 25,
上午见欧盟委员
and the EU commissioner in the morning.
-明白吗  -明白
- Yes? - Yes.
-你告诉其他人了吗  -谁
- Have you told the others? - The others?
孩子们
The kids.
没有
N-No.
告诉他们有什么好处吗
Is there an advantage?
不 我的意思是 只是告诉他们一声
N-No, I mean, just to, you know, just to tell them.
对
Oh. Yeah.
-是吗  -当然
- Yeah? - Sure.
我想欢迎汤姆来到这个家庭
I'd like to welcome Tom to the family.
我没觉得自己失去了一个妹妹
I don't feel like I'm losing a sister.
我也没觉得自己赚到了个哥哥
I don't feel like I'm gaining a brother, either.
我什么都感觉不到
I don't feel anything.
这是一种精神疾病
It's a mental disorder.
叫做边缘人格障碍
It's called borderline personality disorder.
为什么大家都在笑
Why is everybody laughing?
谁想听听单身派对的轶闻
Who wants to hear about the bachelorette party?
-我想听  -想吗
- I do! - Yeah?
那你们运气不好
Well, you're out of luck,
因为什么都没发生 我们只是...
'cause nothing happened, we just...
我们做了针织 沙拉 还有一些瑜伽
we knitted and made salads, did some yoga.
没人会说不同的故事
And no one will tell you different,
因为我们杀了脱衣舞男
because we killed the stripper.
但说真的 我想...
But seriously, I would...
我要感谢我的父亲...
I'd like to thank my dad...
因为我在契约上有义务
because I'm contractually obligated.
不 我真的要感谢你
No, I would actually like to thank you.
还有汤姆 我也要感谢你
And Tom, I would like to also thank
当我的依靠
for being my rock.
你是个好人 威姆士丹
You're a good guy, Wambsgans,
我喜欢和你在一起
and I like hangin' out with you.
那么...
And so...
这一杯... 敬我...
here's a toast... to me...
也敬汤姆
and to Tom.
我只想说
I just want to say
我知道我们从没看对眼过
I know we haven't always seen eye-to-eye,
但是当你父亲把你
but that's difficult when your father's
偷到大西洋对岸时我很难过
stolen you away 'cross the Atlantic.
我知道你可能会觉得
And I know you probably
我是故意想让你哭
think I'm deliberately trying to make you cry
或抢你的风头
or steal your limelight,
但我只想在大家面前告诉你
but I just wanted to tell you, in front of everybody,
你很特别
that you're special,
我按自己的方式爱着你
and, after my own fashion, I love you.
我只想在公开场合说这些
So I just wanted to say that in public,
因为我年纪越来越大
because I'm getting on
我的健康状况可能等不到
and I might not be in good enough health
你再婚的时候说出来
to say it when you remarry.
我... 爱我的妻子
I... love my wife.
我只是...
And I just...
我就是喜欢说"妻子"这个词
I just love saying the word "Wife."
"妻子"
"Wife."
"妻子 妻子"
"Wife. Wife."
"妻子 妻子 妻子 妻子 妻子"
"Wife, wife, wife, wife, wife."
她是我的妻子
So... she's my wife,
而且...
and, um....
她是我的生命
she's my life.
我不会再说下去了
And I'm gonna stop talking now,
因为我觉得我快哭了
because I feel like I'm gonna cry,
现在哭就太疯狂了
and it would be crazy to cry,
因为我现在很开心
because I'm so happy right now.
谢谢大家的到来
So, thank you all for coming,
我爱你们
and I love you all.
我要坐下 我的脚快疼死了
I'm gonna sit down. My feet are killing me.
打扰一下 抱歉 能不能...
Excuse me. Hey. Sorry. Could I...?
好 当然
Yeah. Of course.
你之前发的短信是什么意思
What was that text message you sent before?
某种反建议吗
Some kind of anti-proposal?
"你不做我就不做"
"I won't do it if you won't"?
听着 我刚跟吉尔谈过 听起来
Look, I just spoke to Gil, and it sounds like,
他觉得自己十分机智啥的
well, he thought he was being very subtle and all,
但有事发生了
but something has happened,
我想知道是他妈的什么
and I wondered what the fuck that was.
什么方面的事
Happened with what?
关于掩盖我们知道的事
In terms of burying whatever it is we know
不用再担心泛美网络科技公司
and not being afraid of ATN anymore.
这个观点挺有趣的
Oh. Well, that's an interesting perspective.
我拉你入伙了
I brought you in.
我做了什么
What did I do?
我会让他赢
I'm gonna make him win.
无论如何他都会赢
He's gonna win anyway.
我可能并不认同
I might not agree.
好吧 听着
Well, yeah, look,
我不想装烂好人
I don't want to play the bleeding heart here,
但我和他共事是有原因的
but there is a reason I work with him,
这是因为...
and it's because of...
不平等...
inequality, and...
不平等诶
Oh! Inequality!
好吧 如果你应付不了 那就滚吧
Well, if you can't handle it, then fuck off.
你是谁
Who are you?
我他妈是西沃恩·罗伊
I'm Shiv fucking Roy.
我将拥有两位非常感恩的人...
And I'm gonna have two very grateful people...
下一任总统和我父亲
the next president and my father.
亲爱的
Honey.
对不起 亲爱的
I'm sorry, honey.
对不起 但你要跟你的兄弟们谈谈
I'm sorry, but you need to talk to your brother.
好的
Ok.
你们都需要聊聊
You all need to chat.
打扰一下 小肯
Excusez-moi. Hey, Kenny,
我能跟你说句话吗
can I grab a word with you?
对不起 兄弟...
I'm sorry, bro...
我没有跟你...
I didn't give you the full...
说清楚
full picture.
谢谢 老康
Thanks, Con.
好的
Right.
好 好
Ok. Ok.
所以怎么回事
So what the fuck? Hmm?
爸告诉我们了
Dad told us.
你怎么能这样
How could you?
事情不受我的掌控
It, uh, it was out of my hands.
你可真行
You're a real piece of work.
你的行为就像你他妈是... 人
You act like you're a fuckin'... guy,
装得人模狗样的 但你就是个垃圾 兄弟
like a decent guy, but you're a piece of shit, man.
听着
Look.
我们能开诚布公 对吗
We can talk, yeah?
跟我说话没必要夹枪带棒的
There's no need to talk to me like I'm the enemy.
好像无论我们愿不愿意 都要跟你谈
I think we get to talk to you however we fuckin' want.
事实上 我是被迫走到这个地步的
The fact is, I was, I was forced into this position
这不是我的本意 我不想...
against my wishes, I didn't want to...
可怜的肯德尔
Poor Kendall.
-滚你丫的  -伙计
- Boo-fuckin'-hoo. - Dude,
我会回答你所有的问题
I'll answer any questions you have.
好极了 我有一个问题 你他妈在干吗
Great. I have a question. What the fuck are you doing?
我... 我在尽力拯救公司
I'm... I'm trying to save the company.
用搞死我们的方式
By fucking us. Forever.
听着 如果能行
Look, if this works,
这是毫无疑问的
which undoubtedly it will,
你们都会变得非常非常有钱
you'll all be very, very, very rich,
并且 说句难听点 但这没准是最好的结果
and, I hate to say it, but maybe it's for the best
因为这将不再是一个家族运营企业
for this to no longer be a family-run operation.
不可能 因为 首先
Well, no, because, for one thing,
我们得到的遗产全是股票 所以在此之后
our inheritance is all in stock, so if after this
老爷子发疯把股票弄臭 什么都没有了
Dad goes fuckin' nuts and pisses it all away, nothing.
肯德尔 事实是 我们现在还算可以
Kendall, the fact is, right now we're somebodies.
咱们随随便便都能有几百万美元
Any doof us can have a few million bucks.
-得了  -得了吗
-Come on. - Come on?
你策划了一场收购 你他妈有什么毛病
You plotted a takeover! What the fuck is wrong with you?
要在我大喜的日子
To fundamentally alter
从根本上改变这个家族的性质吗
the nature of the family on my wedding day?
你知道自己有多他妈的自私吗
Do you have any conception of how goddamn selfish you are?!
这不是因为一条破裙子
This isn't about a fuckin' dress.
滚开 我知道这不是因为什么破裙子
Fuck off! I know it's not about a fucking dress!
不是的 这是关于未来的
No, it's not. This is about the future,
我们的未来 这是关于未来千百年的
our future, this is about the next thousand years!
数千年的帝国吗
The Thousand-Year Reich? Uh-huh.
那将永世长存是吗
That will endure for eternity.
醒醒吧
I mean, wake up.
这只是个小动作
This is just a little maneuver.
懂吗 你们没必要感情用事
OK? You don't need to get sentimental.
感情用事 你以为这只是
Sentimental? You think this is
我们感情用事 只为了寻开心吗
us just being sentimental, just for the hell of it?
没想过要在今天... 这样对爸...
The lack of thought to do this to Dad... today...
得了 小西 咱别装了
Come on, Shiv, let's not pretend.
好吗 这和爸无关
Yeah? This isn't about Dad.
这是因为你喜欢权力
This is because you like the power.
它能让你靠近主宰者
It gets you close to the Hill.
还有罗曼 如果没有裙带关系
And Rome, you couldn't get a job in a fuckin' burger joint,
你连破汉堡店都进不去 更别说世界五百强企业了
let alone a Fortune 500, without some nepotism.
然后老康 你只是喜欢沙漠里
And Con, you like the glamor it gives
怪诞畸形秀赋予的魅力而已
to a fuckin' freak show in the desert.
不是 小肯 我可以在家族企业的帮助下
No, Kenny, I could just do with the assistance of the family firm
实现成为总统的壮志
on my ambitions to become President.
就是这样
That's it.
对 正是
Right. Exactly.
你们都他妈活在幻想世界里
You're all living in a fuckin' dream world.
所以...
So...
拷打进行得怎么样了
how's the torture going?
我不需要... 我... 我该走了...
I don't have to... I'm... I ought to go. I...
我知道你们想做什么 好吗
I know what you're trying to do, OK?
我不会伏法的 我现在根本不该和你说话
I'm not gonna let you. I shouldn't even talk to you right now.
我觉得没什么不说话的理由 不管合不合法
Oh, I don't think there's any reason not to, legal or otherwise.
我不会谈这个
I'm not getting into it.
那你不觉得欠我们一个解释吗
So you don't think that you owe us an explanation?
我什么都不欠你 不欠
I don't owe you anything. No.
你一生中有什么不是我给你的
What have you had your entire life that I didn't give you?
我不会谈这个
I'm not getting into it.
这事我做定了 明白吗
I'm doing this thing. OK?
我他妈什么都不欠你
I don't owe you fucking anything.
我真怪自己
I blame myself.
宠坏了你
I spoiled you.
现在... 你毁了自己
And now... you're fucked.
我很遗憾
And I'm sorry.
我很遗憾你是温室的花朵...
I'm sorry you're a hothouse flower...
一文不值
that you're nothing.
你就是结了块的奶油
You're curdled cream.
也许... 你该写本书
Maybe... Maybe you should write a book
或者收集运动卡片之类的
or collect sports cars or something.
至于造福世界 算了吧
But for the world? Nah.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
你生来就不是这块料
You're not made for it.
你比老虎还毒
You're a fuckin' beast.
那个 你还有...
Yo, uh, do you have any more...?
你知道的
Uh-huh. Um, you know,
为了明天也许我们该...
it's just that tomorrow maybe we should bo...
毕竟有场硬仗要打
We got a huge day tomorrow.
-当然  -是的
- Sure. - Yeah.
那你有没有一点点
You got, like, just a little, though,
万一... 万一我们明天想要呢
in case... in case we want for tomorrow?
可能... 我不知道
May... I don't know.
-你想看一眼吗  -没事吧 兄弟
- You want to look? - Are we good, man?
能有什么事 没事 好得很呢
Are we good? Yeah. We're good.
-我们很铁  -是吗 因为桑迪
- We're golden. - Yeah? Because Sandy
想让我们世界时间2点 4点和6点报到一下
wants us to check in at 2:00, 4:00, and 6:00, GMT.
机智 机智
Wise, wise.
是这样 我就想调整一下状态
Yeah, I can just do with a straightener.
缓解压力
Take the edge off.
但我真的没有... 我没剩了 伙计
Yeah, I just don't... I don't have any, man.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry about that.
-...无缘无故  -靠 有人死了吗
- ...for no reason. -Shit. Did anyone die?
我不知道 但没事的
I don't know. But it's fine.
会没事 没人... 对
It's gonna be fine. Nobody... Yeah.
你刚是在... 开玩笑吗
Hey, were you... kidding
竞选总统那事
about the presidential thing?
不是 怎么了
No. Why?
-怎么了  -是啊
- Why? - Yeah.
因为
Because, I mean,
总得来说 大家不喜欢你
generally speaking, people don't like you.
闭嘴 闭嘴 你是个白痴
Shut up. Shut up. You're an idiot.
不是的 我能胜任那份工作 我做得来
No, I could do that job. I can do that job.
但你为什么想... 你想做什么
But why would you even... What do you want to do?
我将发起一场反对"巨大危害"的运动
Well, I would launch a campaign against the Great Dangers.
"巨大危害"有什么呢
Wh-- Eh-- What are the Great Dangers?
其实 这是我从读物里看来的
Honestly, this is from my readings,
而不幸的是 你不能谈它
and sadly, you can't say this
因为准许公开辩论的范围
because the permitted public debate
已经缩小到一个破坚果那么大了
has shrunk to the size of a fucking nut,
但老实说 就是高利贷和俄南癖[手淫]
but, frankly, usury and onanism.
高利贷和鹅鹅...
Usury an... anun...  unoonan...
高利贷和俄南癖
Usury and onanism.
无担保债务和自慰
Unsecured debt and masturbation.
好种子的浪费
The spilling of good seed.
听起来好屌
That sounds dope.
这不是为了公共消费
Well, it's not for public consumption.
这是我从阅读中理解的
I mean, this is from my readings.
好吧 是哦 当然了 那还用说
Well, yes, of course. Obviously.
-而且我不想交税  -好吧 格丽
- And I don't want to pay tax. - Well, duh. Gerri!
亨利·戴维·梭罗: 美国作家 超验主义代表人物
就像一场抗议 就像梭罗
Like a protest, like Thoreau.
我觉得吧 他说得对
He had it right, let me tell ya.
你听说了没 你听到任何消息了吗
Did you hear yet? Did you hear anything?
-关于什么  -日本
- About? - Japan.
有多少...
Like, how many, like...
有多少人死亡 他们发现了多少
how many died, how many did they find?
-听说了 你没听说吗  -没有
- Yeah, you didn't hear? - No.
-没有  -没有 完全没有吗
- None. - None. Like "None" None,
-根本没有吗  -也不是 两人丢了指头
- none at all? - No. Two guys lost thumbs,
可能还有一条胳膊救不活了 但没准能行
and there might be an arm they can't save, but they might.
我的天 所以你... 你他妈在逗我吗
Oh, my God. So you... you're...  Are you fuckin' kiddin' me?
只是一条胳膊跟几根破指头吗
It's just an arm and a couple of fucking thumbs?
-真可悲  -我的天 老天啊
- It's so sad. - Oh, my God, Jesus,
不 那太好了
no, that's great.
几根指头又不会毁掉派对
Not gonna ruin a party over a couple of fuckin' thumbs.
等着 罗曼 你好吗
Hey, wait. Hey. Roman. How ya doin'?
-好极了  -听着 我很抱歉...
- Uh, great. - Listen, I'm sorry...
肯德尔干了那种事...
about Kendall...
没事... 你猜猜...
No... That's... Hey. Guess...
是谁没害死任何人
Guess who just didn't kill anyone,
仅仅让他们丢了几根指头而已
but maybe only lost a couple of thumbs?
-我不知道  -正是在下
- I don't know.  - This guy.
好哇
Hey.
好
我都听说了
Hey, so I heard.
-好吧...  -我就想祝你好运
- Yeah, well... - I just want to say good luck.
-祝我好运  -是的
- Good luck?  - Yeah.
我觉得那地方必须要改变了
The place has gotta change, I feel.
就那些清规戒律
Like the old shit, the nasty politics,
比如... 邮轮航线那事
like, the... the stuff at the cruise lines?
你知道这事吗
You know about that?
我知道是因为我帮忙清理了 但...
Because I helped clean it up, you know? But...
好 你听着...
Hey, so, listen. Um...
你知道在哪可以找到...
Do you know where I can find, uh...
我能用得上的'那种东西'
I could use a little... 'sumpin, sumpin'.
我也希望有 但我
I wish. But I, you know,
我拷贝了几份关键资料
I made copies of a few key documents
关于那档子事的
related to all that stuff,
就怕哪天我遇上麻烦了
in case I got into any trouble at all?
所以我相信 只要是个聪明人
So I would just think, like, anybody would be wise
都会尽力保住我
to keep me in a good role.
格雷格你个狗日的蛋蛋
Greg the motherfuckin' Egg.
瞧瞧你
Look at you.
有人在后面飞大麻
Some guys smoke weed around the back
他们也许知道
I think might know.
马基亚维利主义: 指为达到自己的目的可以不择手段
即实用主义
你个不择手段的混蛋
You little Machiavellian fuck.
我看懂你了 格雷格
I see you, Greg.
我很喜欢
I like it.
太好了
Hell yeah.
你想来谈谈
Hey. Do you wanna talk about
这次收购会如何影响到你的生意吗
how this takeover affects you in the business?
-因为... 我的天  -你真美
- Cause... Ow. God.  - You look amazing.
你是业绩好才进来的
I mean, you're in on merit.
-但如果这成功了...  -你真是太美了
- But if it's successful...  - You look amazing.
情况会很艰难 但我觉得你... 一定可以的
you know, it'll be tough, but I think you... you're good.
我并不在意这些
I don't really care about that.
我现在只关心怎么钻进这条美丽的裙子
All I care about is getting into this beautiful dress.
-如果吉尔上任了...  -我能撕掉它吗
- If Gil takes off... - Can I rip it?
不行 如果吉尔上任了 我都不知道
No. If Gil takes off, I don't even know
自己想不想回去搞政治 尤其是现在...
if I want to go back inside, especially now...
小西 我们开干吧
Shiv. Shh. Let's just fuck.
你太着急了 先生
You're very forward, sir.
-我太着急了  -对
- I'm very forward? Oh. - Yes.
知道吗 我根本不在乎那些计划
You know, I don't care about our plan.
我不是因为那些计划才和你结婚的
I didn't get married to you for the plan,
又或者说... 你懂的
or because... you know,
我只是... 我知道你很强硬 很强势
I just... I know that you're hard and you're tough,
但是我就想和你一起 待在你身边
but I just want to get in, I want in, I want in on you.
懂吗 要不去...
You know? Let's go to...
咱们他妈的去新西兰
Let's go to fuckin' New Zealand,
做牧羊人好了
become sheep farmers.
-牧羊人  -没错
- Sheep farmers?  - Yeah.
-你会潜水吗  -你知道我会的
- Can you scuba?  - You know I can scuba.
那就出发 你到时还能教人潜水 我们出去吧
Well, let's go and teach scuba then. Let's get out!
你觉得呢
You think?
汤姆 我有句话想说
Tom, I gotta tell you something.
我应该早点告诉你的
And I should have told you before.
我之前出轨了
I've had a little number.
你出轨了吗
You had a little number?
是的
Yeah.
而且... 因为我以为
And... you know, because I thought
我们都是成年人了 而且我们有过约定
we were both grownups and we had an agreement.
我们会以成年人的方式来做事
That we were gonna behave in a very grownup manner.
我们有吗
Right. Did we?
当然 我是指
Well, yeah, I mean,
我以为我经常暗示了
I always implied, I thought.
好吧
Ok.
你愿意说是谁吗
Do you want to say who?
如果是我记错了 我真的很抱歉
And if I've got it wrong memory, then I'm really truly fuckin' sorry.
是纳特吗
What it Nate?
从现在起 我希望咱们能开诚布公一切
I want everything to be open and honest from now on.
我能送他回家吗
Can I send him home?
-当然可以  -好的
- Yeah, sure.  - Good.
汤姆
Tom.
我...
I'm...
我想我... 就...
I just think I'm... just..
我可能不适合一夫一妻制的婚姻
I'm just not sure I'm a good fit for a monogamous marriage.
好吧...
Right...
-好的  -这可以吗
- OK.  - Is it OK?
-这么对你说可以吗  -当然可以
- Is that OK to say to you?  - Of course.
我有点儿希望...
Yeah. I kinda wish...
我觉得... 我们应该在新婚夜前谈这事的
I guess... maybe we'd talked about this before our wedding night.
对 我也是
Yeah. Me too.
我俩刚勾搭上的时候
I just think I was in such a total mess
我是一团糟
when we hooked up,
而我是那么需要你
and I needed you, so much,
我知道这很糟糕
I was in a very bad way,
我们也获得了有效的公司业务
and we've got the business angle that works,
这些... 我们都做得很好 还有个计划
we're... good on that, we have a plan.
但至于我们的关系
But in terms of the relationship,
我就在想
I'm just wondering
有没有一个契机能让与众不同的事
if there's an opportunity for something different
发生在这万念俱灰的生活中
from the whole box set death march.
万念俱灰的生活
The box set death march.
没错
Yeah.
你懂的 不同形式的夫妻关系
You know, just a different shape of relationship.
也许会很刺激呢
It could be exciting.
好吧
Right.
也许吧 我猜
Maybe, I guess. Yeah.
-会很刺激的  -的确刺激
- It's exciting!  - It's exciting.
没错 因为我们把别的一切都毁了
Yeah! Because we've torn everything else down.
没错吧 爱情就是最后一块冰箱贴
Right? Love is the last fridge magnet left.
好吧 这是什么意思
Right. How do you mean?
我是说 爱情就是...
Well, I mean that love is...
它就像二十八样不同的东西
it's like 28 different things,
然后它们全被扔进同一个袋子
and they all get lumped in together in this one sack,
而那个袋子里还有很多别的东西
and there's a lot of... things in that sack,
需要被清空
it needs to get emptied out.
有恐惧 嫉妒还有仇恨
There's fear and jealousy and revenge,
控制欲 还有...
control, and...
它们都他妈被一个很好看的包装纸盖着
they all get wrapped up in really nice fuckin' wrapping paper,
从外面看上去真的很美好
and it just looks really lovely and nice,
-一旦你打开它...  -是的 没错 你是对的
- but when you open it up... - No, no. You're right.
这就是...
It is. It's...
爱情啊 狗屁不如
Love. It's bullshit.
没错
Yes!
但我... 我真心爱你
But I... I do love you.
我也爱你...
I love you too...
日了狗
Fuck.
草他大爷的
Fuck!
-我想脱掉这裙子  -把它脱了
- I want to get this dress off. - Get the dress off.
喂
Hey.
你好
怎么了 兄弟
What's up, man?
你在这后面干嘛呢
What you, uh, what you got goin' on back here?
-没什么  -没事的 没事儿
- Nothin'.  - No, it's cool, it's cool.
在那边都能闻得到你这味
You can just smell it from down there.
闻起来像是好大麻
It smells like the kind bud.
我是不是刚才看见你撞枪口了
Hey, didn't I see you get some shit earlier?
你还好吗 我爸就是个混蛋
You OK? My dad's a fuckin' bastard.
是的
Yeah.
我没事的 他们付我钱了
No, yeah, it's cool. They paid me up.
-付给你全款了吗  -是的
- For like the whole shift? - Yeah.
还给了点好处
And a sweetener.
-挺好的  -真的挺好的
- Nice. - It's actually pretty good,
我现在能回家了
'cause now I can just go home.
-挺好 挺好  -是啊
- Nice. Nice. - Yeah.
兄弟...
Dude...
我这样问会不会有些奇怪...
would it be weird to ask if...
你想来一口吗
Do you want a smoke?
-当然可以  -来吧
- Yeah, sure. - Here.
但是... 你懂的
But also... you know,
在今晚这样的超级派对上
for the party, like, big party tonight,
我在想 你不会正好有点
and I just wondered, you don't have a connection
药粉[毒品]吧
for some powder, do you?
-有吗  -有的
- Yeah? - Yeah.
♪ 窈窕淑女 ♪
♪ Uptown girl ♪
♪ 她住在那高档的住宅区 ♪
♪ She's been livin' in her uptown world ♪
而且我可能不太适合... 当你的军师
And also I'm probably not the right strategist... for you.
你觉得自己是民主党人吗
Would you consider yourself a Democrat?
你可别想把我套进去 纳特
Now, don't box me in, Nate.
兄弟 我能和你聊聊吗
Dude. Can I get in?
我们正... 聊着呢
We're just... talkin'.
-我不在乎  -行吧
- Whatever. - Yeah.
好的 以后再聊
Ok. Tbc.
行 好吧
OK. All right.
-老兄  -老兄 还好吗
- Hey, man. - Hey, man. How are you?
挺好的 多棒的夜晚啊
I'm good. What a night.
-是啊  -太棒了
- I know. - Lovely.
听着 我很抱歉
Listen, I'm so sorry,
但是你的住宿似乎出了点问题
but there seems to be a little mix-up in your accommodation.
-是吗  -是啊
- Right. - Yeah.
不好意思 你没地方住了
I'm sorry, but there's nowhere for you to stay.
那好吧 我自己会处理好的
OK, well, I'm sure I'll figure something out.
可以 不过我劝你最好直接离开
Right. But it might be smart for you to leave directly,
-去找住所  -你是认真的吗
- to find something. - Are you serious?
没错 我认真的
Yeah. I'm serious.
我懂了
I get the message.
没事的 可以
It's fine. OK.
我们还是保持冷静
Let's just keep things cool,
你应该平静下来
I think you need to stay calm.
大家都是成年人 小西也是成年人...
We're grownups, Shiv's a grownup...
我觉得你可以去死了
I think you need to go fuck yourself.
如果再让我看到你和小西在一间屋子里
And if I ever see you in the same room as Shiv again,
我会雇人打断你的腿
I will pay men to break your legs.
如果我进监狱了 当然我不会
And if I go to jail, which I won't,
随他的便
so be it.
好吧 好的
OK. Fine.
好吧
Fine.
我这就走
I'm gonna head out,
先让我喝完这杯酒...
I'm just gonna finish this...
这酒是我爸妈惠赠的
My mom and dad made a contribution to the wine,
我真的不太想让你继续喝了
so I'd really rather you didn't drink anymore.
-你在搞笑吧  -抱歉 谢谢
- Are you kidding? - Excuse me. Thank you.
倒回来... 纳特
Put it back... Nate.
-别这样  -倒回来 纳特
- Come on. - Put it back, Nate.
快他妈把我的酒倒回来 快点
Put my fuckin' wine back. Now.
给我他妈的倒回来
Put it the fuck back.
这才对嘛
There you go.
别他妈整幺蛾子
Don't make a fuckin' mess.
♪ 现在她来寻找乡村男孩 ♪
♪ And now she's looking for a downtown man ♪
♪ 那就是我呀 ♪
♪ That's what I am ♪
爽
Yep.
等等 我... 等下
Wait, I... Hang on.
这是什么
What is this?
氯胺酮
Ket.
-别吧  -K粉
- No. - Special K.
不 今晚我想要点... 不同的感觉
No, I need a different... different vibe tonight.
我想嗑点可卡因
I was after some coke.
我的确认识些人
I mean, I know someone,
但算了吧 这可是K粉啊
but no, this is ket.
是啊 但你认识人是吗
Right. But you know someone?
-是的  -我们去找他们
- Yeah. - Let's go for it.
-好吗  -好吧
- Is that cool? - OK,
我不太确定自己现在能否开车
I don't know if I should drive right away.
不行吗 我能开
No? I can drive.
-可以吗  -当然
- Yeah? - Yeah, sure.
-好吧  -我可以的
- OK. - I'm good.
来吧
Ok.
你还好吗 老兄
You OK, bud?
我没事
I'm fine.
好了
Ok.
你还好吗 老兄 兄弟
You OK, bud? Hey. Buddy?
还能认清路吗
Gonna be able to find the way?
可以的
Yeah.
通会儿风吧 好吗
Let's get some air in here, yeah?
你能搞定吗
You all right there?
可以 就是这个傻逼变速杆
Yup, just fuckin' stick shift.
你都开自动档的车吗
You're used to an automatic?
而且 我不怎么开车
Plus, I don't drive that much.
-为什么  -因为我太有钱了
- Why not? - Because I'm incredibly rich
去哪儿都有司机送
and I mostly get driven everywhere.
-你很有钱  -没错
- You're incredibly rich? - That's right.
我他妈阔绰得超乎你的想象
I am fuckin' loaded beyond your wildest imagination.
-还有多远  -我该绑架你吗
- How much further is this? - Should I kidnap you?
是啊 要是你他妈还能走 你就应该绑架我
Yeah, if you can fuckin' walk, you should kidnap me.
-我知道有座房子  -你知道有座房子
- I know a house. - You know a house?
能他妈关住我的房子吗
Like a place to fuckin' keep me?
是的
Yeah.
那有个牛棚
It's got a cow shed.
我可以把你关在那儿
I could keep you in there.
那里只有个波纹铁皮顶棚
It's only got a corrugated iron roof,
你会感觉冷得要死
so it's gonna be fuckin' cold.
你在乎什么呢
I mean, what do you care?
是啊 可不是吗
Yeah, exactly.
小心
Look out!
♪ 狂欢吧 狂欢吧 让我们纵情快乐吧 ♪
♪ And do it, and do it, let's live it up and do it ♪
♪ 狂欢吧 狂欢吧 狂欢吧 ♪
♪ And do it, and do it, and do it ♪
♪ 我们狂欢吧 我们狂欢吧 我们狂欢吧 狂欢吧 狂欢吧 ♪
♪ Let's do it, let's do it, let's do it, do it, do it ♪
♪ 我们来 我们跳... ♪
♪ Here we come, here we go... ♪
-你来了  -妈妈
- Hello. - Hi, Mom.
小淘气
Naughty one.
罗曼告诉我了
Roman told me.
好吧
Right.
我认为你一点也不坏
I don't think any the worse of you.
-不坏吗  -不坏
- No? - No.
那就好
Well, good.
跳支舞 来吧
Have a dance. Go on.
罗里 跳支舞吧
Rory, have a dance.
-老弟 你好吗  -好得很
- Man. You good? - Yeah.
你别来烦我们
Why don't you just leave us.
谢谢 再见 再见
Thanks. Bye. Bye.
-你来啦  -老康
- Hey. Hey! - Con.
你是来上朝了吗
You holding court over here?
我正和两位美女聊天呢 是的 没错
I am talking with two beautiful women, yes, I am.
你好 我是肯德尔 很高兴见到你
Hi. Kendall. Nice to meet you.
-这是我弟弟肯德尔  -你好
- My brother Kendall. - Hi.
好的
Yeah.
听着 我很抱歉
Listen, I'm sorry.
-你懂的 那个...  -我知道
- You know, about... - Yeah.
我真心的
I am.
没事
Ok.
过来 哥们 给个拥抱
Come here, buddy. Give me a hug.
你们怎么还醒着 早就该去睡觉了
What are you guy doing up? It's way past your bedtime.
-睡不着  -中午睡过觉了
- Couldn't sleep. - We slept this afternoon.
还在倒时差吗
Oh, you're jet-lagged, yeah?
你之前去哪了
Where have you been?
瞧瞧你俩
Look at you two.
他们刚刚在找你
Hey, they were lookin' for ya.
-知道  -他们想跳舞
- Yeah. - They want to dance.
-你们看着挺精神  -你想跳吗
- You guys look great. - You wanna dance?
你们两个小机灵豆
Look at you goobers.
♪ 如何驱逐我的忧伤 ♪
♪ How to chase my blues away ♪
♪ 我迄今尚可支撑 ♪
♪ I've done all right up to now ♪
♪ 是日光给了我力量 ♪
♪ It's the light of day that shows me how ♪
♪ 每当夜幕降临 ♪
♪ And when the night falls ♪
♪ 寂寞开始叫嚣 ♪
♪ Loneliness calls ♪
♪ 我想与某人共舞 ♪
♪ Oh, I wanna dance with somebody ♪
♪ 一起体温蹿升 ♪
♪ I wanna feel the heat with somebody ♪
♪ 我想与某人共舞 ♪
♪ Yeah, I wanna dance with somebody ♪
♪ 某个爱我的人 ♪
♪ With somebody who loves me ♪
♪ 我想与某人共舞 ♪
♪ Oh, I wanna dance with somebody ♪
♪ 一起体温蹿升 ♪
♪ I wanna feel the heat with somebody ♪
♪ 我想与某人共舞 ♪
♪ Yeah, I wanna dance with somebody ♪
♪ 某个爱我的人 ♪
♪ With somebody who loves me ♪
-一套公寓吧  -你是说你喜欢它喽
- A flat, I suppose. - You mean you like it?
当然 是套好公寓
Why yes, as a flat.
我们不就是要公寓吗
And a flat's what we're looking for.
亲爱的 理智点
Darling, do be sensible.
一年内... 好吧 两年...
In a year's time... well, two year's, yes...
我们就得考虑贷款
we'll think about mortgages,
我会拼命多赚点好去旅游
and I'll work up the strength for the traveling bit,
但我们得把可用现金都来炒股
but we're gonna need all available cash for Hope!
我处女膜不好了
Bad news about my hymen.
-咋了 -它没了
- Yo? - It's gone.
早 肯德尔
Hi, Kendall.
-早啊 小肯  -早上好 肯德尔
- Hey, Kenny. - Morning, Kendall.
很高兴见到你
Good to see ya.
早上好 苦瓜脸先生
Morning, Mr. Fuckface.
-早  -早哇
- Hey. - Yo.
-你好吗  -挺好的
- You good? - Yeah, yeah, pretty good.
有点宿醉
Little hung over.
好吧
Good, OK.
这里服务人员的感觉
Yeah, kind of a weird vibe with the, uh,
有点怪怪的 像霍比特人
with the service folks, like the Hobbit-y people?
有个酒水招待员 好像是
There's like, I guess, a caterer,
那人出了车祸 又嗑高了
a guy, like, got in a crash, and was high,
我也不清楚 没人清楚怎么回事
or, like, I don't know, nobody knows.
但是情况很操蛋
But some bad shit went down.
-真的吗  -对
- Really. - Yeah.
但是据说 家族...
But the word is, like, the family...
家族的原话是我们别因此坏什么事
the family line is that we're not gonna let it spoil anything.
-好吧  -你懂的吧
- Right. Oh, good. - You know?
-好  -行
- Good. - Yeah.
THE SUB-MAN
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠
但是 他...
But, uh, he...
他还好吗
So, um... is he OK?
他...
He...
他好像死了
I guess he died.
对 太倒霉了
Yeah. Bad shit.
真的惨
Really sad.
炒蛋怎样了 变硬了没
How's the scrambled egg? Has it congealed?
你说什么
What's that?
炒蛋怎样了
How's that scrambled egg?
在那放了一小多时了
It's been sittin' there for like an hour.
肯德尔 洛根想和你谈谈
Kendall, Logan wants a word with you.
-来了 儿子  -来了
- Hey, son. - Hey.
谢了 老科
Thanks, Col.
坐吧
Sit.
想来点什么吗
You want something?
不用 我... 挺好的 我...
Oh, no, I'm... I'm good. I-- I just, uh...
我很好
Mm-- I'm good.
你昨晚过得愉快吗
Did you have an acceptable evening?
还行 你懂的
Uh, uh-huh. Ya know.
我整晚没睡... 组织我的防御计划
I was up all night... organizing my defense.
当然了
Right.
不知道你听说没
I don't know if you know,
那位和我起争执的招待员
but the caterer I had an issue with
昨晚死了
died last night.
太可怕了
Oh, that's terrible.
-你已经知道了吗  -我...
- Did you know? - I...
我知道 因... 因为我... 刚听说
I knew. I- I knew bec... because I... just found out.
但确实 太... 令人吃惊了
But, uh, it's a... it's a shock.
这样
Uh-huh.
我们的手下...
So, our guys, uh...
手下一个人
one of our guys,
找到一张你房间的房卡...
found a keycard to your room...
就在这孩子落水的地方附近
near where this kid went into the water.
对
Yeah.
-他可能...  -还有...
- Maybe he, uh... - And... And, uh,
-他可能...  -阿米尔昨晚...
- maybe he... - Amir saw you...
看到你 浑身湿透
last night, rather damp.
警察正和卡洛琳在一起
The police are here with Caroline.
我们只想让你检查
We just want you to check
昨晚有无东西失窃
if you had anything stolen last night.
好... 好像没有吧
I don't... I don't think so.
也许你该再查查
Maybe you should check again.
这孩子
This kid,
我想可能是个小偷
I think he might have been a thief
闯进了你的房间...
who broke into your room...
拿了你的卡
and took your card.
对
Right.
我来处理这事
Let me handle this.
我认识这帮警察 我们很熟
I know the guys, they know our guys,
他们都是好人
they're good guys,
我们会告诉他们丢了啥
so we'll let them know what was taken.
行 好的
OK. Right.
爸 我...
Dad, I-- I-- I...
这事是挺烦心的
Yeah. This has been quite stressful.
要不你坐我的车
Why don't you get in my car
然后我们送你上飞机
and we'll drive you to the plane.
你就可以放松了
And then you can relax.
我不知道...
I, uh, I don't know...
没事 我感觉那挺好
Yeah, yeah, I think that would be good.
好 我是说...
Right. I mean, uh...
...没人做了... 错事
...nobody did anything... wrong,
你懂的 听起来...
and, uh, ya know, it sounds like, so...
对
Yeah.
告诉桑迪你退出
Tell Sandy you're out.
告诉斯图伊这把戏简直垃圾
Tell Stewy the thing looks like a shit show.
去沙漠里
Go to the desert,
清醒一下
dry yourself out.
你的状态很不对
You have not been yourself.
没什么... 我不觉得...
There's nothing... I don't... I don't think, um,
而且... 我当时不在那...
and... I wasn't there, so...
这可能是你人生的决定性时刻
This could be the defining moment of your life.
它会毁了一切
It'd eat everything.
富家子弟杀人...
A rich kid kills a boy...
你会永远无法翻身
you'd never be anything else.
或者 这事也能回归本真
Or, you know, it could be what is should be:
即什么都没发生
nothing at all.
不过是... 发生在美妙婚礼上
A sad... little detail
一个可悲的小细节...
at a lovely wedding...
父亲与儿子
where father and son
在此和好
are reconciled.
你是我儿子
You're my boy.
你是我最棒的儿子
You're my number one boy.
对不起
I'm sorry.
没事 没事
No, no, no, no.
科林
Colin?